<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conditions on Selenium Compose</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/conditions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conditions on Selenium Compose</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/conditions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Attribute</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/conditions/attr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/conditions/attr/</guid>
      <description>Properties attr has the following available options
   Name Description Type Required     location Web element location string true   selector Methods by which to find elements string false   name Web element attribute name string true   not_empty Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s attribute is not empty bool false   is Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s attribute is equal to the given string string false   contains Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s attribute contains to the given string string false   starts Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s attribute starts to the given string string false   ends Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s attribute ends to the given string string false   matches Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s attribute matches to the given pattern string false   ignore_case Perform case-insensitive comparisons if the flag is true bool false   count Expected elements count Count false   timeout Wait until the expected condition has been satisfied Duration false    Usage attr condition accepts only a map of values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invisibility</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/conditions/invisibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/conditions/invisibility/</guid>
      <description>Assert Web Elements invisibility.
invisibility allows to expect invisibility of Web Elements present in the DOM. A Web Element is considered to be invisible if it is not viewable on the page due to its styling or size.
Key Invisibility goes under invisibility key.
Properties    Name Description Type Required     location Web element location string false   selector Methods by which to find elements string false   count Count of expected invisible elements Count false   timeout Wait until the expected condition has been satisfied Duration false    Usage invisibility accepts a string or a map of values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/conditions/presence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/conditions/presence/</guid>
      <description>Assert Web Elements presence in the DOM in any state.
presence allows to expect Web Elements presence in the DOM.
Key Presence goes under presence key.
Properties    Name Description Type Required     location Web element location string false   selector Methods by which to find elements string false   count Count of expected present elements Count false   timeout Wait until the expected condition has been satisfied Duration false    Usage presence accepts a string or a map of values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/conditions/text/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/conditions/text/</guid>
      <description>Assert a Web Element content or value.
text allows to expect Web Elements text, content or value to be equal to the expected value, contain, start, end with the piece of string or match the given pattern. If the element is an input its conditions are being checked against its value otherwise the element content.
Key Text goes under text key.
Properties    Name Description Type Required     location Web element location string false   selector Methods by which to find elements string false   notempty Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s content or value is not empty bool false   is Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s content or value is equal to the given string string false   contains Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s content or value contains the given string string false   starts Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s content or value starts with the given string string false   ends Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s content or value ends with the given string string false   matches Expect the element&amp;rsquo;s content or value matches the pattern string false   ignore_case Perform case-insensitive comparisons if the flag is true bool false   count Count of expected elements Count false   timeout Wait until the expected condition has been satisfied Duration false    Usage text condition accepts only a map of values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Title</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/conditions/title/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/conditions/title/</guid>
      <description>Assert the current page&amp;rsquo;s title.
Key Title goes under title key.
Properties    Name Description Type Required     is Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s title to be the given string string false   contains Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s title to contain the given string&amp;rsquo; string false   starts Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s title to start the given string&amp;rsquo; string false   ends Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s title to end with the given string&amp;rsquo; string false   matches Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s title to end with the given string&amp;rsquo; string false   ignorecase  bool false   timeout Wait until the expected condition has been satisfied Duration false    Usage Inline Use inline syntax to expect the current title contains the piece of string.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Url</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/conditions/url/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/conditions/url/</guid>
      <description>Assert the current page&amp;rsquo;s url. All comparision are performed in case-insensitive manner for url.
Key Url goes under url key.
Properties    Name Description Type Required     is Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s url to be the given string string false   contains Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s url to contain the given string&amp;rsquo; string false   starts Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s url to start the given string&amp;rsquo; string false   ends Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s url to end with the given string&amp;rsquo; string false   matches Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s url to end with the given string&amp;rsquo; string false   schema Expect the current page&amp;rsquo;s url schema is the given string (http or https)&amp;rsquo; string false   ignorecase  bool false   timeout Wait until the expected condition has been satisfied Duration false    Usage Inline Use inline syntax to expect the current url contains the piece of string.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visibility</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/conditions/visibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/conditions/visibility/</guid>
      <description>Assert Web Elements visibility.
visibility allows to expect visibility of Web Elements present in the DOM. A Web Element is considered to be visible if it is viewable on the page.
Key Visibility goes under visibility key.
Properties    Name Description Type Required     location Web element location string false   selector Methods by which to find elements string false   is Expect the element visibility whose content or value is equal to the given string string false   contains Expect the element visibility whose content or value contains the given string string false   starts Expect the element visibility whose content or value starts with the given string string false   ends Expect the element visibility whose content or value ends with the given string string false   matches Expect the element visibility whose content or value matches the given string string false   ignore_case Perform case-insensitive comparisons if the flag is true bool false   count Expected visible elements count Count false   timeout Wait until the expected condition has been satisfied Duration false    Usage visibility accepts a string or a map of values.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>